Enate allows you to orchestrate end to end
services across people and bots.
Let's take a digitization example.
Here we've got an invoice being emailed in
which gets picked up by smart OCR bots to
scan categorize and extract data
before a UI path bot updates the data into
an ERP system.
At every point, if the bot goes wrong or it's
not confident in the outcome,
Enate let’s you put a human in the loop
to help resolve.
You can configure end-to-end orchestrations
like this in Enate using the super-simple
Builder tool.
Here's the invoice getting emailed in.
In the background, there's scheduled bots
which pick up that mail and categorize, extract
and validate the data.
In this case the confidence levels from the
bot aren't strong enough so Enate flips the
work over to the human in the loop.
Team members working in Enate automatically
pick up the next most important activity against
SLAs.
Here we surface the ‘smart OCR Validation
Station’ user interface inside an Enate
smartcard.
So regardless of how the human gets in the
loop, Enate’s their go-to place.
Validation Station displays the specific issues
to the agent and helps them correct the data
as necessary.
Once they're happy with their changes,
they mark as complete and we pass this onto
a UIPath bot to update an ERP system as the
next part of the process.
Logged into Enate digital operations platform
as a team leader, I can easily track this
activity.
Here we can see our Bot Pluto as it picks
up the work.
Enate acts as a governance platform
where managers can see which resource is doing
what work, where, when and why - whether that's
a person or a bot.